{
  "id": "019-social",
  "title": "Social & Polite Talk",
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "atsiprašau",
      "choices": [
        "sorry",
        "thanks",
        "hello",
        "bye"
      ],
      "answer": "sorry",
      "tts": "atsiprašau"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "prašau",
      "choices": [
        "please",
        "sorry",
        "yes",
        "no"
      ],
      "answer": "please",
      "tts": "prašau"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "ačiū",
      "choices": [
        "thank you",
        "sorry",
        "hello",
        "bye"
      ],
      "answer": "thank you",
      "tts": "ačiū"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "malonu",
      "choices": [
        "nice",
        "bad",
        "late",
        "slow"
      ],
      "answer": "nice",
      "tts": "malonu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "geras",
      "choices": [
        "good",
        "bad",
        "slow",
        "fast"
      ],
      "answer": "good",
      "tts": "geras"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "atsiprašau"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "prašau"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "ačiū"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "malonu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "geras"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "atsiprašau",
      "choices": [
        "sorry",
        "thanks",
        "hello",
        "bye"
      ],
      "answer": "sorry",
      "tts": "atsiprašau"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "prašau",
      "choices": [
        "please",
        "sorry",
        "yes",
        "no"
      ],
      "answer": "please",
      "tts": "prašau"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "ačiū",
      "choices": [
        "thank you",
        "sorry",
        "hello",
        "bye"
      ],
      "answer": "thank you",
      "tts": "ačiū"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "malonu",
      "choices": [
        "nice",
        "bad",
        "late",
        "slow"
      ],
      "answer": "nice",
      "tts": "malonu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "geras",
      "choices": [
        "good",
        "bad",
        "slow",
        "fast"
      ],
      "answer": "good",
      "tts": "geras"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "atsiprašau"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "prašau"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "ačiū"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "malonu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "geras"
    }
  ]
}